<ArrayOfFirstSteps xmlns:i="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/backend.Models"><FirstSteps><Id>2</Id><description>Application documents for Incoming Exchange Students</description><information>Passport </information><link>empty</link></FirstSteps><FirstSteps><Id>3</Id><description>Required documents for your application</description><information>You will need the following documents:Proof of language proficiency (Spanish or English)</information><link>empty</link></FirstSteps><FirstSteps><Id>4</Id><description>Application deadlines</description><information>Winter semester: May 15. Summer semester: November 15</information><link>empty</link></FirstSteps><FirstSteps><Id>5</Id><description>Bachelor´s Degree Program</description><information>Recognition of Qualifications for Admission to a Higher Education Institution. You must submit this application and your documents to the university by 15 July of the year in order to ensure that your application meets the deadlines.   Certification of German Language Proficiency (does not apply for degree programs in English language) must be provided by applicants from non-German-speaking countries.   Separate entrance requirements apply for applicants from China, Mongolia, and Vietnam wishing to study at Nuremberg Tech. You must present a certificate from the Akademische Prüfstelle (APS) of the German Embassy in, Peking, Ulan Bator, or Hanoi, respectively.</information><link>empty</link></FirstSteps><FirstSteps><Id>6</Id><description>Master´s Degree Program</description><information>You need the following for a Master’s degree program: A completed post-secondary degree, usually with above average marks or grades, or an equivalent degree. A certification of adequate German language skills (e.g. DSH 2, TestDaF 4), if required. Current, valid requirements are available for your reference in each degree program’s study regulations and exam regulations. Apply online for the degree program you have selected and submit translations of your credentials and supporting documents. The examination boards of the respective Master’s degree programs decide all admissions to their programs.</information><link>empty</link></FirstSteps><FirstSteps><Id>7</Id><description>International Degree Program</description><information>Nuremberg Tech also features special international Bachelor’s and Master’s degree programs for foreign students, in which lectures are presented in English.   The Bachelor' s degree programs International Business and International Business and Technology &amp; the Master' s programs International Marketing and International Finance and Economics have their own admission requirements.</information><link>http://www.th-nuernberg.de/institutionen/fakultaeten/betriebswirtschaft/studienangebot/international-business-study-programs/bachelor-ba-international-business-internationale-betriebswirtschaft/page.html http://www.th-nuernberg.de/institutionen/fakultaeten/betriebswirtschaft/studienangebot/international-business-study-programs/bachelor-beng-international-business-and-technology/page.html http://www.th-nuernberg.de/institutionen/fakultaeten/betriebswirtschaft/studienangebot/international-business-study-programs/master-ma-international-marketing/page.html http://www.th-nuernberg.de/institutionen/fakultaeten/betriebswirtschaft/studienangebot/international-business-study-programs/master-msc-international-finance-and-economics/page.html</link></FirstSteps></ArrayOfFirstSteps>